Erhan GURSACLI

Powercoders Participant

Rte cantonale 18, 1898 St-Gingolph | 05.11.1985 | Residence permit B (Turkey) erhan.gursacli@powercoders.org | +41 77 962 78 42

GitHub | LinkedIn

Languages: English (C2), French (B1), Turkish (mother tongue)

IT skills: Intermediate: MS Office, HTML, CSS

Elementary: JavaScript, Python

SUMMARY

Passionate about learning, highly motivated in self-improvement besides strong communication skills. Bachelor and master degrees in Linguistics along with 9 years of professional experience in the field of forensic linguistics. As a plus, 3 years of experience as an English teacher. With the attractiveness of the endless universe of IT, seeking a career in a position which offers intellectual and professional satisfaction.

WORK EXPERIENCE

09/2021 – 03/2022 Server, The Restaurant of Formation Center for Refugees, Vouvry

(Switzerland)

- Welcome and Service

07/2018 – 04/2021 Teacher, American Culture Language School, Ankara (Turkey)

- Teaching English for age groups ranging from 12-45

- Integration of social media (mainly Twitter) to language learning activities.

07/2007 – 09/2016 Linguist, Forensic Police Laboratory, Ankara (Turkey)

- Conducting linguistic analyses on forensic cases.

- Responsible for the quality management system of the unit.

EDUCATION

04/2022 – 06/2022 Powercoders – Coding Academy for Refugees, Zurich (Switzerland)

- Foundations in HTML, CSS, JavaScript; specialization tracks upcoming

09/2008– 06/2015 MSc in Linguistics, Ankara University, Ankara (Turkey) 09/2003– 06/2007 BSc in Linguistics, Hacettepe University, Ankara (Turkey)

HOBBIES

Playing old strategy games such as Red Alert, Age of Empires.

Listening Classical and Rock Music Nature walk along the river or lakeside

REFERENCES

Christina Gräni Lead Company Relations Romandie, Powercoders

christina.graeni@powercoders.org, +41 78 626 35 82